(Leonard:)We're not living together.
- Are you sure?
- How could I not be sure?
(Penny:)Well, let's find out.
(Leonard:)Don't you think if a woman was living
with me, I'd be the first one to know?
(Penny:)Oh, sweetie, you'd be the last one
to know about it.
(Sheldon:)Hmm.
(Penny:)Cute dresses.
(Penny:)I bet this looks great on you.
(Leonard:)We're not living together.
(Penny:)Okay. Hmm.
(Penny:)Scented candles, fuzzy slippers. Ooh.
(Penny:)Floral bed sheets.
(Leonard:)We're not living together.
(Penny:)Okay, moving on.
Uh, who are these guys at Disney World?
(Steph:)Uh...
(Leonard:)The big dog is Goofy.
(Leonard:)And the older couple with the mouse ears,
I have no idea.
(Leonard:)We're not living together.
You're gonna go down swinging, huh?
(Penny:)All right. Well, we got your body lotion,
your In Style magazine, your jewelry box.